

CONTACT

Born 1985 in Caracas, Venezuela

Paraguay 1873
Buenos Aires - Argentina

+54 9 1127927778

wilfredo1285@gmail.com

@freakdroid github.com/freakdroid

I don't have

SKILLS

Javascript

ES6

React.js

Node.js

Angular 6

Python

MongoDB

AWS

English

WILFREDO ROBERTO PÉREZ

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

About me, I'm a Venezuelan System Engineer, with more than 8 years of experience creating awesome software and coding with passion. I love coding Javascript, researching and developing on new technologies. I promote the team work and the good communication because these are important in any company, trying to share with my coworkers my lessons learned to improve ours skills everyday.

EXPERIENCE

Fullstack Javascript Engineer / Frontend Developer - Vates S.A Since September 2017 (Actual Job)

Creating awesome stuff using Angular 7, React.js, Node.js and AWS.

Javascript Engineer (Remote - Freelancer) - ISeatz (New Orleans, Luisiana)

March 2017 - September 2017

Improving, Debuging and Creating new stuff for America Express Travel Site.

Javascript Engineer (Remote - Freelancer) - Azumo (San fracisco, Califronia)

July 2016 - January 2017

Creating bots using Node.js in Facebook.

Fullstack Developer .Net - Mediconecta.CA (Caracas, Venezuela) Agust 2014 - October 2015

Working on Telemedicine platform to help the people.

EDUCATION

Systems Engineer

September 2002 - June 2007, Systems Engieer, IUP "Santiago Mariño", Caracas, Venezuela.

High School

September 1997 - April 2002, High School, UEP "Liceo Independencia", Caracas, Venezuela.